[Music]
[Música]
Gloria Camila's story in moments
historia de gloria camila en instantes
while 4 hours ago I
mientras hace 4 horas
don't know how you interpret this. Look, they
no sé cómo interpretas ustedes esto mira
have their story in history, but
tienen su historia en la historia pero
for Pisces there
para piscis
are no limits. When they bet on something, they
no hay límites cuando apuesta por algo
bet with all the consequences, and
apuesta con todas las consecuencias y
when they separate from something, too. And when they
cuando se separa de algo también
bet on something, they
y cuando se cuando apuesta por algo
bet with all the consequences, and
apuesta con todas las consecuencias y
when they separate from that something, they also go,
cuando se separa de ese algo también va
go for what they're going to. Do you understand it the
va por lo que va a verdad lo entendéis
same way I do? Do you understand
igual que yo
it the same way I don't? Do you understand it the
lo entendéis igual que yo no
same way I do? I'm
lo entendéis igual que yo
going to look at birthday dates, let's see,
voy a ver fechas de cumpleaños a ver
Pisces,
piscis
and if we were talking
y si estaríamos hablando
between March 15th and April 14th,
entre el 15 de marzo y el 14 de abril
okay? Between March 15th and April 14th,
vale entre el 15 de marzo y el 14 abril
okay.
vale
Gloria
gloria
Camila's birth date is
camila
February 21st. Sanz.
el 21 de febrero
Gloria Camila is not a Pisces. Gloria
sanz gloria camila no es piscis gloria
Camila is not a Pisces.
camila no es piscis
Gloria Camila is not a Pisces.
gloria camila no es piscis
Antonio David's
de nacimiento antonio david
birth date is not clear to me. Antonia Vi's birth date is not clear to
no me sale la fecha de nacimiento
me. April 24th.
me sale el 24 de abril
April 24th, they don't explain much,
el 24 de abril no explicitan poco
5 years in a hurry,
5 año de prisa
the children are flowers, October 13th.
los hijos flores 13 de octubre
Who the [ __ ], Pizzi?
quién [__] pizzi
by la moreno
por la moreno
olga moreno it was her birthday recently
olga moreno fue su cumpleaños hace poco
I remember we sent her a
que me acuerdo que le mandamos un
message recently October 3rd
mensaje hace poco 3 de octubre
five years
cinco años
and if it's in February let's see if it comes out here
y si es en febrero a ver si me sale aquí
that from March 15th to April 14th
que del 15 de marzo al 14 de abril
gloria camila no
gloria camila no
gloria camila comes out on
gloria camila sale el veintitantos de
February 20th no species February 21st there are no
febrero que no especies 21 de febrero no
bikes look
hay bicis mira
February 21st
21 febrero
zodiac
zodiaco
pizzi
pizzi
dot it's pisces and then it comes out wrong for me
punto es piscis y entonces me sale mal
on google when I search hey
en google cuando busca
look don't let the devil laugh at the
oye mira que no se ría el [__] de la
lie
mentira
here March 15
aquí 15 de marzo
20 March 15 April 14
20 15 de marzo 14 de abril
okay it refers to her at the end to her
vale se refiere a ella a su fin a su
zodiac sign well
signo zodiacal
then
pues entonces
gloria camila says that when when she
gloria camila dice que cuando que cuando
bets on something she
apuesta por algo
bets with all the consequences and
apuesta con todas las consecuencias y
when she separates from something also
cuando se separa de algo también
what what do you
qué
think what does this mean how does she
qué creéis usted qué significa esto como
interpret it and family
la interpreta y familia
how does she interpret it and I don't leave it to
como la interpreta y no se lo dejo a
your free choice
vuestra libre elección
I'm going
yo me voy
[Music]
[Música]